AFAMEFUNA ANEKEH

Email: <u>afam262@gmail.com</u> | 862-596-7814 | Round Rock, TX 78665 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/afam | GitHub: https://github.com/Afam-26 | Portfolio: https://afam-26.github.io/

SUMMARY

After my first degree in Public Administration; I started my working career as a Sales Manager at a tire shop where I worked closely with upper management, met sales goals and lead a small team of sales associates. There, is where I gained my leadership skills and became a strong organizer and coordinator.

I then left my home country of Nigeria to study at Austin Community College (ACC). While completing my associate degree at ACC, I worked at AT&T as a tech support analyst. My team was responsible for making sure AT&T network was always functional for their clients and end users. There, is where I learned the art of troubleshooting, conflict resolution and meeting up with high demands.

After graduating from ACC with an Associate degree in LAN System Security and certificate in Network Admin, I joined Whole Foods Market as Sr. Service Desk Analyst. There, is where I improved my leadership skills with the ability to motivate and influence others to deliver best results. I learned how to communicate effectively by creating a transparent understanding for all parties involved. I am capable of expressing technical ideas and information in a user-friendly language. Proficiency at understanding, articulating and solving both complex and complicated problems. Successfully identified roadblocks and possible setbacks on a project by working with team members to develop a resolution strategy.

While working at Whole Foods Market, I develop passion in coding, web application and API. This motivated me to enroll for Full Stack Web Development with University of Texas (UT). With my newly develop skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and responsive web design, I was able to create my Portfolio and improve online search engine optimization.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, GIT, Github, HTML, CSS, JQuery, Media Queries, APIs, The Command Line.

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Password-Generator

https://github.com/Afam-26/Password-generator.git | https://afam-26.github.io/Password-generator/

- This application is created to assist users with generating a random password based on criteria they have selected. Once user with creating a unique and strong password.
- Language Used: HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Halloween Quiz Game

https://github.com/Afam-26/Halloween-Game.git | https://afam-26.github.io/Halloween-Game/

- A timed quiz on that stores high scores, so that player can gauge his/her progress and compare it with their peers.
- Language Used: HTML, CSS and JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

Whole Foods Market – Austin, TX Senior Service Desk Technician

2017 - 2020

- Supports leadership in monitoring call queue, ensure consistent call queue availability, and actioning escalations as required by leadership.
- Operate and maintain server and network systems to satisfy company requirement.
- Support the Cybersecurity and Client Support Team as a subject matter expert in modern Microsoft Windows Platforms.
- Maintain Active Directory Domain Service, DNS, and DHCP services.
- Managed employee and agent account profiles and resolved any conflicting permission issues.
- Resource for Help Desk, providing real-time guidance to technicians and team members.

AT&T Inc - Austin, TX Tech Support

2016 - 2017

While completing my associate degree at ACC, I worked at AT&T as a Tech Support Analyst. My team was responsible for making sure their network was always functional for their end users. There, is where I learned the art of troubleshooting, conflict resolution and meeting up with high demands.

Chinek Tires Enterprise – Delta State, Nigeria Sales manager

2011-2014

I started my working career as a sales manager at Chinek Tyre Enterprise, where I worked closely with upper management, met sales goals and lead a small team of sales associates. There, is where I gained my leadership skills. I learned the importance of dealing with different personality types and needs.

• Boosted sales revenue %60 by creating new distribution channels and opportunities.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate - University of Texas; Austin, TX | 2020

LAN System Network Admin Certificate - Austin Community College; Austin, TX | 2017

Associate degree in LAN System Security Admin - Austin Community College; Austin, TX | 2017

Bachelors degree in Public Admin - Institute of Management & Technology, Enugu, Nigeria | 2009